Hey, you ready to go?
Oh, yeah.
Let me just finish this.
JOEY:
Hey, Ross.
Check this out.
Yeah, I can't do that.
What are you doing?
Hey, have you seen this?
It's our new alumni Web site
for college.
It's cool. You can post
messages for people,
let everyone know
what you're up to.
Oh, great, a faster
way to tell people
that I'm unemployed
and childless.
It's, it's actually
kind of interesting
to find out
what people are doing.
Remember Andrea Rich?
That tall girl that
wouldn't sleep with you?
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Well, her Internet
company went under,
and she lost an ear
in a boating accident.
Bet she'd sleep
with you now.
No, I already e-mailed her.
Let me see what you
wrote about yourself.
Oh.
"Doctor Paleontology,
two kids..."
Wait a second,
you split with Carol
because you had
different interests?
I think you split
with Carol
because you had one
very similar interest.
You know what? I'm going
to finish this later, okay?
Let me just grab my coat.
Okay.
What, did you think
you learned how to do it
in the last two minutes?
Maybe we finish
this for him.
"Also, I cloned
a dinosaur in my lab.
"She's now my girlfriend.
"I don't care what society says,
it's the best sex
I've ever had."
( snickers )
And.... send.
No, no, whoa!
You can't do that to him.
All right, let's go.
Dude.
I think you made it clear
you can't be trusted
with the ball inside the house.
And... send.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey...
how was basketball?
Well, it was a lot of fun.
Yeah, right up until
Chandler got a finger
in the eye.
Oh, no. Who did that?
Chandler, yeah.
Hey.
Uh, Rach.
Yeah?
What's Huggsy doing
in the crib with Emma?
Oh, well, she was
just crawling around
and she found him.
So, I just let her sleep
with him.
That's all right, isn't that?
Oh, oh, of course. Yeah.
It's a stuffed animal, you know.
It's for kids, not for adults.
I know that.
Joey, you-you sure?
I mean, I know how much
you love him.
Rachel, let's, let's be clear,
okay? I do not love Huggsy.
I like him a normal amount.
RACHEL:
All right.
Well, Emma loves him.
Yeah, well, why wouldn't she?
He's a wonderful person.
( door shuts )
Hi.
Oh, hey, Phoebe.
How you doing?
You feeling better?
Breaking up sucks.
Oh, I really miss Mike.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I've tried everything
to make myself feel better;
even tried writing
a song about it,
but I can't think of anything
that rhymes with...
( pained wail )
Hey, Monica, I'm going to need
your help getting through this.
Hey, you're not going
to need my help?
Well, no, when I get to the
point where I'm ready to hear
cruel mocking jokes about Mike,
I'm going to come to you.
Oh, great, 'cause I've already
thought of three-- four!
I just thought of a fourth.
Okay, I mean I know
I did the right thing.
You know, Mike never wants
to get married,
and I shouldn't be in a
relationship that has no future.
But pretty soon
I'm going to miss him so much,
I'm going to want
to see him again,
and you have to stop me
from doing that.
Okay, you got it.
Unless... Am I being
too crazy about this?
All right, so, you know,
there's no future,
but that doesn't mean
we still can't have fun.
You know what?
Forget what I said.
Really? All right,
if that's what you want.
That was a test,
and you just failed.
Damn it! Rookie mistake.
I have sex
with dinosaurs?!
I believe
I read that somewhere.
Not only is it not funny,
it's physically impossible.
Okay? Depending
on the species,
I'd have to have
a six-foot long--
It's not funny!
I respectfully disagree.
I can't believe you put
that on my alumni page.
Who cares?
Nobody reads those things.
Well, you better
hope not,
because I just read what
you put on your page today.
I don't have a page.
Oh, oh, oh, I
respectfully disagree!
JOEY ( thinking ):
Look at you,
all sweet and innocent,
sleeping like an angel...
with Emma's chubby little hands
wrapped around you.
It's okay, Emma,
you stay asleep.
( cries )
Step away
from the crib!
I have a weapon!
It's okay!
It's okay, Rach, it's me!
Put down the scrunchie.
What are you doing?
Well, I heard Emma stirring,
so-so I came in to make sure
she could reach Huggsy.
Oh.
Oh, thanks.
All right, well,
now that I'm up,
I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
Okay, there you go, sweetie,
oh...
This isn't over.
All right,
wait a second.
Why would Ross tell
everyone in your class
that you are "as gay
as the day is long"?
Because I told everyone
he slept with dinosaurs.
Well, that's clearly a joke.
This could easily
be true.
( phone ringing )
Would you get
that, please?
People have been calling
to congratulate me all day.
Hello?
No, he's not here.
Yeah, this is his wife.
Yeah, well, it came as
quite a shock to me, too.
Well, I guess
I should have known.
Yeah, I mean he just kept
making me watch Moulin Rouge.
Hang up.
Hang up!
And that was a great movie.
I'm so going to get back
at Ross.
Oh, yeah, this will show him.
Here we go.
What are you doing?
Oh, you'll see, my friend!
I'm dead?!
And so young.
Posting that I died?
That really isn't funny.
Well, how you died was funny.
Oh, please. Hit by a blimp?
It kills over one Americans
every year.
Unbelievable.
My classmates are going to think
I'm dead.
My professors, my.... my parents
are going to get phone calls.
You're messing
with people's feelings here.
Oh, you want to talk
about people's feelings?
You should have heard how hurt
Professor Stern was yesterday
when I told him I wouldn't be
able to go with him to Key West!
You've really crossed the line
here, but that's okay.
That's okay,
'cause I'm on my way
to buy some Photoshop software
and a stack of gay porn.
That's right, your coming out
is about to get real graphic!
Oh, God, I wish
Mike were here.
Okay, if
Mike were here,
what would the two
of you be doing?
What are you, animals?
It's 4:00 in the afternoon.
I got to call him.
Just-just to talk to him.
There's no harm in that.
Phoebe, that's
how it starts.
"I don't need to eat the cake,
I'll just smell the icing.
Why not just a little sliver,"
or, "Okay, just a-a slice
or two."
You know, the next thing
you know, you're 210 pounds,
and you get wedged in
going down the tunnel slide.
Phoebe, honey,
I know this is hard.
Look, if you talk to him,
then you're really going
to want to see him.
And if you see him,
you're going to want to get
back together with him.
I know that's not
what you want.
Give me your phone.
Here.
And now your cell.
Okay.
Here you go.
This is your cell phone?
Yes.
This is your current cell phone?
It reminds me
of a simpler time.
Phoebe, where's your purse?
Hey! No, no!
Give it to me!
You can't have it.
No.
I'll go in there.
Oh, yeah, right.
Phoebe, come here!
No.
Give it to me!
Whoa! You're craz...
It's gone.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ah, Aha!
Damn you, Monica
Geller hyphen Bing!
Hey, hey,
look who's here.
It's Joey,
and he brought home a friend.
Joey, Emma's right here.
You promised
not to bring girls home
in the middle of the day
anymore.
No, no, no, no, it's not a girl.
It's... a brand-new Huggsy!
Aw...
That's so great.
Now Emma has two Huggsies.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, Emma has one Huggsy.
The new Huggsy, huh?
The other Huggsy, I don't know,
I guess I'll just take him back.
Oh... oh,
you know what?
When I was a little girl, I had
a little pink pony named Cotton.
Oh, I loved her so much,
I took her everywhere.
I would braid her tail and...
Make the transfer.
Now, should I
be concerned
that a button fell off the old
Huggsy, and I can't find it?
Oh, no, don't worry about it,
I swallowed that years ago.
Hey, hey.
( crying )
Oh, what?
I don't think
she likes the new Huggsy.
But it's the same.
I think she wants
the old one back.
Yeah, but he's the same.
Joey, come on.
But he's the same.
Joey...
You're not the same.
Aha!
You know, it's a lot less
surprising to do that
after I've buzzed you
into the building.
So, Phoebe...
why are there men's shoes
by the door?
Those are my shoes.
Oh. Well, when you get over this
breakup, we need to go shopping.
Look, Monica,
I really appreciate
you checking in on me,
but I'm actually feeling
a lot better.
Really?
Yeah.
I just kind of want
to be alone right now.
( knock on door )
Who's that?
I ordered Chinese food.
What are the chances?!
One billion Chinese people,
and they send Mike!
What are you
doing here?
Phoebe called me.
Phoebe!
I'm sorry, I broke down.
I wanted to see him.
Damn it, Phoebe,
how did you even call him?
There's a speaker phone
on the base unit.
Base unit!
Think, Monica, think!
Look, if I want to see Phoebe,
and she wants to see me--
This doesn't concern you.
Sorry. I guess I was thrown off
by the mention of my name.
Look, guys, you
can't do this.
It's just going
to make getting
over each other
that much harder.
Not if nothing happens.
Why can't... why can't we
just hang out as friends?
Sure.
If you're just going
to hang out as friends,
then, then maybe
I'll join you.
Yeah, I'm your friend
and Mike's friend.
Yeah.
Sit down.
MONICA:
Oh, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Make room for your friend.
There you go. Ah.
So how have you been?
I've been
pretty good.
You look really
beautiful.
Thanks.
You look good, too.
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
This is dangerous territory.
Keep it clean.
So how's the
piano playing going?
Actually, I've
been playing
a lot of love
songs lately.
I've missed you.
I've missed you, too.
You know, on the way
over here,
I saw this drunk guy
throw up...
and then
a pigeon ate it.
Hey. Ross.
Look, I just wanted
to apologize for...
Don't tell me
you actually made
those gay pictures of me.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Check this out.
Huh.
So, that's what I'd look
like if I worked out...
and was being serviced
by a policeman.
You're not going to actually
send these out, are you?
Uh, actually, no,
I don't need to
because your little "Ross is
dead" joke didn't work, okay?
There were no responses.
Nobody posted anything
on the Web site.
Nobody called my parents.
So, the joke,
my friend, is on you.
Nobody called,
nobody wrote anything.
Nobody cares that I'm dead.
Oh, my God.
Nobody cares
that I'm dead?
Oh, come on, you know
that's not true.
What are you
talking about?
You get 60 responses just for
coming out of the closet.
I didn't get one response,
and-and I'm dead.
Well, the gay community
is a lot more vocal
than the dead community.
I can't believe this.
Not even my geology lab partner?
And I carried that guy!
All right, look, let's
think about this, okay?
Do you really think
that people are going to
disturb your family
at this tragic time?
That people are going to post
condolences on a Web site?
This isn't about people
not caring that you're dead.
This about people not having a
decent outlet for their grief.
You're right,
there isn't a decent outlet.
Right, I mean,
come on.
I'm sure if you had a funeral
or memorial service,
tons of people would come.
Exactly!
Ross, what are you,
what are you,
what are you doing?
You're having a memorial
service for yourself?
What?
No. That would be stupid.
You're having it for me.
Ross, don't press that.
Don't press that!
Too late, too late.
It's sent.
Oops, sorry, so's that picture
of you and the policeman.
I'm trying to put
Emma down for a nap.
Have you seen Huggsy?
Uh, original or crappy?
Original.
No, sorry, haven't seen him.
Then what's that big lump
under your covers?
It's Monica, okay?
That is not Monica.
All right, fine!
It's original Huggsy.
I know Emma wants him,
but he's mine, and I need him.
She's being unreasonable.
Joey, there is a reason that
Emma loves that stupid penguin
so much!
( gasps )
Oh, don't cover its ears!
It's because it reminds her
of her Uncle Joey.
It does?
Yeah, and she's
comforted
by him because she loves
her Uncle Joey so much.
Really? She, she loves me?
Oh, yeah.
But you know what?
If you need Huggsy, don't worry.
Emma will totally understand.
I won't, but whatever.
Okay, wait, wait, w-wait, wait
a minute, wait a minute, Rach.
I mean if, if... if Huggsy
means that much to Emma, then...
Well, she can have him.
Aw... oh, sweet, I knew
Uncle Joey would step up.
Look, Emma, look
who's back...
No, forget it,
forget it, I can't do it.
Are you kid-- you're
going to take Huggsy
away from a little child?
How do you think I got him
in the first place?
All right, you two,
I'm going to go
to the bathroom.
Now, I don't want anything
going on while I'm gone.
All right, here's a few things
you can discuss:
Mucus, fungus, and the idea
of me and Ross doing it.
I've missed
you so much.
No, I'm not going to ask
you to get back together
because I know we want
different things,
but just to be with
you one more night.
I know,
I want that too,
but is that going
to make it too hard?
It can't be any
harder than this.
I mean, if I had known
the last time I saw you
would be the last time I...
I would have stopped
to memorize your face,
the way you move...
everything about you.
If I had known the
last time I kissed you
would be the last time...
I never would have stopped.
Kiss him, you fool!
What?
Didn't you hear that speech?
If you don't kiss him,
then I will.
I've missed you so much.
I knew you'd be here!
Aah, crap.
Who, who is this?
It's my friend Manny.
I asked him to keep
me away from you.
Hey, that's what
I'm doing for Phoebe.
Well, you're not doing
a very good job.
Excuse me?
What's with the kissing?
Hey, at least I knew
where my guy was.
Oh, yeah, yeah, thank
God you were here
to oversee
all the kissing!
You didn't hear the speech.
I've heard the speech.
If he knew it was going to be
the last time he saw her...
Hey, it was
very moving.
You're just heartless.
You're weak.
You're... weird.
Your pants are undone.
Oh!
Where'd they go?
Oh. Damn it!
Oh, we blew it.
I blame myself.
And I blame you, too.
It's been an hour,
and not one
of my classmates
has shown up?
I tell you, when I actually die,
some people are going
to get seriously haunted.
( knock on door )
There you go.
Someone came.
Okay, okay, I'm,
I'm going to go hide.
Oh, this is so exciting,
my first mourner.
Hi.
Glad you could come.
Please come in.
Hi.
You're Chandler Bing, right?
I'm Tom Gordon.
I was in your class.
Oh, yes, yes.
Let me take your coat.
Thanks.
Uh, I'm, I'm so sorry
about Ross. It's...
Well, at least he died
doing what he loved.
Watching blimps.
Who is it?
I don't know--
some guy, Tom Gordon.
I don't remember him.
But, then again,
I touched so many lives.
So did you
know Ross well?
Oh, actually,
I barely knew him.
Yeah, I came because
I heard Chandler's news.
You know if he's
seeing anyone?
Yes, he is. Me.
What? ( stuttering )
Oh. Oh, can I ask you
a personal question?
How, how do you shave
your beard so close?
Okay, Tommy, that's
enough mourning for you.
Here we go.
Bye-bye.
All right.
Hey, listen... call me.
Okay.
I'm dead and
no one cares?
I look like a man?
Please, one ridiculous
problem at a time.
This isn't
ridiculous.
Look around. No one's here.
You gave them
one day's notice.
Not everyone
in our class
checks the Web site
every day,
and Monica, it's probably
the way you stand.
All right.
Still, somebody
must have seen it.
I mean, I went to that school
for four years
and I didn't have
an impact on anyone?
Well, that's
not true.
You had
an impact on me.
I mean it's
15 years later
and we're still
best friends.
Doesn't that count
for something?
Man.
( knock on door )
Oh, great, more party
boys for Chandler.
I'm sure it's
somebody for you.
Now go hide.
Hi.
I'm here for Ross Geller's
memorial service.
Kori?
Kori Weston?
Yeah.
You look amazing.
And you are?
Chandler. Chandler Bing.
I'm not gay,
I'm not gay at all.
You are
married,
though.
Don't listen to him.
He's in a
really bad mood.
I can't believe
that Ross is gone.
It is just so sad.
Oh, I didn't know
Ross and you were so close.
Oh, we weren't,
but we had one class together.
He was such a great guy,
and he talked so passionately
about science.
I always remembered him.
I'm sure that would
mean a lot to him
and if heaven has a door,
I'm sure he's pressing
his ear up against it
and listening intently.
I thought so many times about
calling him and asking him out.
I guess I really
missed my chance.
No, you didn't!
I'm still alive!
Kori, I, I
know this is a big
surprise for you.
It's a long story,
but the things you just said
really made my day.
I mean, the fact that you
are here means more to me
than, than if this room
were filled with people.
You sick freak!
Who does that?
I can't believe
I had a crush on you!
( door slams )
Did you hear that?
Kori Weston had a crush on me.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
No, Mom, I am not dead.
No, I know it's not
something to kid about.
Anyway, it was just a practical
joke between Chandler and me,
but it's over, okay?
Actually, no,
even if I had died,
you would not be left childless.
Monica?